Register of the Pathfinder Press Publications, 1922-2014
Hoover Institution Archives
- INCREMENTAL MATERIALS, PART II (Box 50-52)
  - [ Making History: Interviews with Four Generals of Cuba’s Revolutionary Armed Forces. Persian translation.] 2001. 233 p. (Box 51)
  - Barnes, Jack. [ A Sea Change in Working-Class Politics. Persian translation.] 2002. 57 p. (Box 51)
  - Trotsky, Leon. [ Marxism and Terrorism. Persian translation.] 2003. 57 p. (Box 51)
  - Waters, Mary-Alice. [ Feminism and the Marxist Movement. Persian translation.] 2003. 111 p. (Box 51)
  - Barnes, Jack. [Their Trotsky and Ours. Persian translation.] 2004. 184 p. (Box 51)
  - Sankara, Thomas. [ We Are Heirs of the World’s Revolutions. Persian translation.] 2004. 102 p. (Box 51)
  - Lenin, V. I. [ Imperialism, the Highest Stage of Capitalism. Persian translation.] 2005. 167 p. (Box 51)
  - Dobbs, Farrell. [ Teamster Rebellion. Persian translation.] 2006. 310 p. (Box 51)
  - Barnes, Jack. [ Washington’s Assault on Iraq: Opening Guns of World War III. Persian translation.] 2007. 215 p. (Box 51)
  - Engels, Friedrich. [ Socialism: Utopian and Scientific. Persian translation.] 2007. 118 p. (Box 51)
  - Novack, George. [ Genocide against the Indians. Persian translation.] 2007. 73 p. (Box 51)
  - Barnes, Jack. [ Capitalism’s Long Hot Winter Has Begun. Persian translation.] 2009. 144 p. (Box 51)
  - Marx, Karl and Friedrich Engels. [ The Communist Manifesto. Persian translation.] 2009. 99 p. (Box 51)
  - Seigle, Larry. [ Washington’s Fifty-Year Domestic Contra Operation. Persian translation.] 2009. 114 p. (Box 51)
  - Barnes, Jack. [ Cuba and the Coming American Revolution. Persian translation.] 2010. 169 p. (Box 51)
  - Barnes, Jack. [ Malcolm X, Black Liberation, and the Road to Workers Power. Persian translation.] 2010. 163 p. (Box 51)
  - Waters, Mary-Alice. [ Is Socialist Revolution in the U.S. Possible? Persian translation.] 2010. 91 p. (Box 51)
  - [ The First and Second Declaration of Havana. Persian translation.] 2011. 135 p. (Box 51)
  - Trotsky, Leon. [ The Revolution Betrayed. Persian translation.] 2011. 351 p. (Box 51)
  - Waters, Mary-Alice and Martin Koppel. [ Capitalism and the Transformation of Africa. Persian translation.] 2012. 185 p. (Box 52)
  - Choi, Armando, Gustavo Chui and Moises Sio Wong. [ Our History Is Still Being Written: The Story of Three Chinese-Cuban Generals in the Cuban Revolution. Persian translation.] 2014. 289 p. (Box 52)
  - [ The Cuban Five. Persian translation.] 2014. 125 p. (Box 52)
  - [ “I Will Die the Way I’ve Lived.” Persian translation.] 2014. 35 p. (Box 52)
  - [ Voices from Prison: The Cuban Five. Persian translation.] 2014. 104 p. (Box 52)
  - Hansen, Joseph, Evelyn Reed and Mary-Alice Waters. [ Cosmetics, Fashion and the Exploitation of Women. Persian translation.] 2002. 236 p. (Box 52)
  - Waters, Mary-Alice. [ Teté Puebla: The Mariana Grajales Women’s Platoon in Cuba’s Revolutionary War. Persian translation.] 2003. 154 p. (Box 52)
  - Reed, Evelyn. [ Problems of Women’s Liberation. Persian translation.] 2004. 220 p. (Box 52)
  - Reed, Evelyn. [ Sexism and Science. Persian translation.] 2005. 324 p. (Box 52)
  - Guevara, Che. [ Che Guevara Speaks. Persian translation.] 2007. 223 p. (Box 52)
  - Reed, Evelyn, [ Woman’s Evolution. Persian translation.] 2009-2010. 2 volumes (Box 52)